southmoonunder.com 2016-12-26

# eCommerce Solutions On-Demand | Demandware Privacy Policy | South Moon Under

## **Privacy Policy**

* * *

At South Moon Under, we respect the privacy of our customers and the visitors to our website. This statement describes the current information gathering, sharing and privacy practices for our website, [www.southmoonunder.com](http://www.southmoonunder.com/).

Collection of Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that identifies you individually or allows us to contact you directly (personal information).

We may ask for personal information when you purchase a product, enter a contest, request a service, complete a survey, subscribe to a news, or engage in some other activity on our site. In connection with these activities, we may ask you for contact information such as your name, telephone number, and email address.

When you visit our website, we collect standard information about your hardware and software such as your IP addresses, browser type, operating system, pages visited on our site, referring and exit pages, and the dates and times of the visits.

This site visitation data is used to administer the site and provide general statistics regarding the use of demandware.com. Site visitation data is never linked to your personal information, and we do not use it to identify you individually without your permission.

## **Use of Personal Information**

We will keep any and all information collected from you at this site strictly confidential and we will not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise share your personal information with third parties for their promotional use without your permission.

We will use the personal information you give us to fulfill the services and provide the products you request from us. This may include sending information that you have requested, or contacting you about products and services that you have purchased. If you do not opt-out of communications from South Moon Under, we may send you marketing notices including promotions of our products and services. You can opt-out of communications from South Moon Under at any time (see "Control of Personal Information" below).

We sometimes contract with other companies to provide services such as packaging and mailing information, answering user questions, or processing credit card transactions. We will only provide these partners with the information they need to conduct their services, they will be prohibited from using the information we provide for any other purpose and we will require them to observe the intent of this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your personal information when we reasonably believe that it is required by a law or legal process and to protect and defend our rights and interests and the rights and interests of our affiliates, suppliers, or users. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply these terms and conditions or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, an acquisition by another company, or a sale of all or a portion of our assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Notifications of such a transition will be made using the mechanisms described in the "Changes to this Statement" section below.

## **Control of Personal Information**

You can confirm, change, or update personal information you have provided to us by contacting us directly at [service@southmoonunder.com](mailto:service@southmoonunder.com) with your request.

If you want to opt-out of communications from the company, you can do so by emailing your request to [service@southmoonunder.com](mailto:service@southmoonunder.com). If you change your mind, you can opt-in again, by emailing this same address. When you opt-out of promotional communications from us, you may still receive service messages (such as an order confirmation), legally mandated notices, and critical messages that relate to the ability to use services you have purchased from us.

## **Security of the Information We Collect**

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information, and we use a range of technologies and procedures to protect your personal information. For example, we store personal information in a secure, limited access facility; sensitive information transmitted to us through our store (such as a credit card number) is encrypted for transmission using the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. The SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us.

## **Protection of Children's Privacy**

southmoonunder.com is a general interest website, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

## **Privacy and Online Forums**

Information you post in online forums on the site is accessible to other people who can access the forums and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. Personal information stored in your forum profile will not be displayed in the forum.

## **Privacy and Tell-a-Friend Forms**

When you use a tell-a-friend form on the site, we ask for the friend's name and email address. We will use this information to automatically send the specified email message to the friend. We will not use this information to contact the friend in the future. We will retain the information you provide for tracking purposes. If someone notified through tell a friend wishes to have their information removed from our database they can contact us at [service@southmoonunder.com](mailto:service@southmoonunder.com).

## **Use of Cookies and Clear gif Technology**

When you visit our site, a cookie may be saved on your computer (if your computer accepts cookies), and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. We use cookies to help us collect the site visitation data described above and in some cases to deliver specialized content. A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of our website use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. We do not correlate this information with data about individual users, nor do we share this information or sell it to any third party.

If you prefer not to receive cookies on our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any area of our website.

We may also use Web beacons, clear gif technology, or action tags as mechanisms to collect aggregate site visitation data by tracking how users navigate to and through our website. We may also use this technology to track the delivery of HTML email messages. This data is collected exclusively for use in our marketing and research.

## **Enforcement of this Statement**

If you have questions about the policies described in this statement, please email us directly at [service@southmoonunder.com](mailto:service@southmoonunder.com).

## **Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites. If you use these links, you will leave our website. When you access a non-southmoonunder.com website, even one that may contain the South Moon Under logo, please be aware that we do not control the content and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of that site and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of each site you use. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our website. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.

## **Changes to this Statement**

We may from time to time update this privacy statement. When we make these updates, we will change the "last updated" date listed at the top of the statement. If we make a material change to this statement that affects our use of your personal information, we will update users by placing a more prominent notice on our home page.

## **Contact Information**

We welcome your input on our privacy policy. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [service@southmoonunder.com](mailto:service@southmoonunder.com).

South Moon Under  
ATTN: Privacy  
619 Franklin Ave.

Berlin, MD  21811

888-660-6071
